In today's economy everybody is trying to save some money.
Even when it comes to drinking.
How are you?
My name is Jeff Klein and I'm a bartender and vodka connoisseur here at Beak's Old Florida and I'm going to tell you what's the best vodka for the price.
Now for me it comes down to taste, versatility, how easy it blends with anything I want to do it with, and of course how expensive it is.
For me all of those are summed up in Skyy.
Skyy Vodka, fairly inexpensive, you can usually get it from anywhere around eleven dollars to fifteen dollars in most your grocery stores and liquor stores.
Some of the best things about it are going to be the flavor, affordability, and accessibility.
You can find it almost anywhere.
So my suggestion is next time you're throwing a party and want to bring that vodka home, go out to any liquor store, look for the clear, easily distinguished blue bottle of Skyy vodka and it's a cannot miss for the price.
So, my name is Jeff Klein, vodka connoisseur and bartender here at Beak's Old Florida and that is the best vodka for the price.